Hey.
We're just here
to say goodbye.
We're off to Ohio.
Oh, right, your
adoption interview.
Yep. We're going
to meet the lady
who could be carrying
our baby.
I can't believe it.
When you guys come back
you're gonna have a baby.
That is so weird.
And so incorrect.
She's only a couple
months pregnant.
And she liked
our application,
but who knows if
she's gonna like us.
Oh, come on.
She's going to love you guys.
Thank you, but we're really
trying not to get our hopes up.
And a lot could still
get in our way.
Yeah, I mean, this girl could
decide against adoption,
or she could like
another couple better...
What are you going
to name the baby?
I could develop a condition
in which I talk and talk
and no one hears a word.
But just think, okay?
What if everything goes right?
What if this woman
does pick you guys?
Oh, my God.
She's gonna pick us.
So we're standing firm on
the not getting our hopes up?
No, I know things
could still go wrong.
But if they don't,
if this works out,
we're gonna have a baby,
Chandler. A baby!
Yes, but...
Oh, my God, it's gonna work!
We're gonna make it work!
I'm gonna be a mommy
and you're gonna be a daddy!
I'll see you, suckers.
I'm gonna go get me a baby!
Aw, screw it.
I'm gonna be a daddy!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, who's Phoebe with?
I want to say someone
I'm gonna have sex with.
Hey.
So, uh, who's your friend?
Oh, that's Sarah.
No, don't you get any ideas,
okay?
I'm not setting you up with
any more of my friends.
Whoa, whoa, why?
Because
you'll date her once,
sleep with her,
and then forget she exists.
Name one friend of yours
that I did that with.
Mandy.
Mandy, huh?
Uh...
Really hot blonde, big boobs?
No.
Maybe why I don't remember her,
huh?
Do you think I'm someone else?
Okay, I may not have treated
your friends well in the past.
But I have grown up a lot.
Really. Honest.
Rach?
Yeah, believe it or not,
it's true.
When Joey and I were together,
he was wonderful.
He was thoughtful and mature.
And for the one week
that we went out,
he didn't sleep
with anybody else.
Growth.
Fine. I'll give you her number.
Okay, thank you.
And I promise you
I will not forget this one.
Mandy.
Sarah!
Sarah.
Hey.
Hi.
Hey, you guys, I need
some fashion advice.
How does this look?
Well, it's a little low.
Pick it up a little.
Little bit more.
There you go.
Now throw it away.
Come on, this looks good.
Ross, please.
Trust me.
I buy 30 fashion magazines
a month.
Now, I don't know
who's running for President
or who that NATO guy is,
but I do know
you have to get as far away
as you can from that hat.
Damn it.
I have this date tomorrow night
and I have to look cool.
You know, if you
want fashion help,
Rachel and I are going
shopping tomorrow.
You're more than welcome
to come with us.
Really? That would be great.
I mean, I have to do something.
She kind of teased me
about how I dress.
I can see why.
Nice shirt.
You're wearing the same shirt.
Stupid Gap on every corner!
Please make yourselves
comfortable
and I'll be back in a moment
with Erica.
Okay, thank you.
Well, this is it.
Are you okay?
Yeah. It's just
weird, you know?
It's like, uh,
"Hi, I'm Chandler.
May I have the human
growing inside you?"
You're going to be great.
Well, obviously.
Monica, Chandler,
I'd like you to meet Erica.
Hi. It is so,
so nice to meet you.
Thank you so much for
agreeing to see us.
I'll let you get acquainted.
Okay.
Thanks.
So it's Monica
and Chandler?
I only know you
as file CRW 33815-D.
That's what our
friends call us.
Gosh, you know, you're just
such an amazing couple.
It's kind of intimidating.
I don't know about that.
Are you kidding me?
I mean, it's enough
that you're a doctor...
but on top of it,
you're married to a reverend.
I don't think
that's exactly...
Let her finish, Doctor.
Hey.
Oh, my friend Sarah
had a great time last night.
Yeah, so you going to call
this one back?
No.
But what are you talking about?
Sarah's great.
Oh, really?
You want to know what
your "great" friend did?
We were out to dinner, okay?
We were getting along,
having a really nice time.
I was thinking
she was really cool.
And then, out of nowhere...
( spooky music plays )
That's it?
That's why you won't
go out with her again?
So she took a few fries.
Big deal.
Hey, look, it's not about
a few fries.
It's about what
the fries represent.
What?
All food!
Well, I'm sorry.
I can't believe I set you up
with such a monster.
Hey, look, I take a girl out,
she can order
whatever she wants.
The more, the better, all right?
Just don't order a garden
salad and then eat my food.
That's a good way
to lose some fingers.
Oh, thank God
you're here.
Listen to this.
So, Joey and my friend
are out last night,
they're having dinner.
And she reaches over
and takes a few of his fries...
( gasps ):
Oh, no.
What?
You know about the plate thing?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Joey doesn't share food.
I mean, just last week
we were having breakfast
and he had a couple of
grapes on his plate...
You wouldn't let her
have a grape?
Oh, no, not me. Emma.
Joey doesn't share food!
Well, I still think
that is a stupid reason
not to call someone again.
You are calling her.
And if you need to,
then just get an extra plate
of fries for the table.
I like that.
A sharing buffer.
Yeah, I'll order
some extra fries,
maybe a plate
of onion rings.
Yeah. Yeah.
And a shrimp cocktail.
And some buffalo wings.
And maybe, maybe
an individual pizza.
And some mozzarella sticks...
What were we talking about?
Wow, this place is awesome.
You know what,
we should just go.
I'm not going to find
anything here.
This stuff is ridiculous.
Oh, this place is great!
Wow.
Rach, come on, I'm not going
to wear any of this.
Nothing silver.
Wha...?
Nothing with hair.
( gasps )
And nothing
with padlocks on it.
Ross, look, okay?
I know that some of
this stuff is out there,
but I mean, come on,
look at this.
Look at this sweater.
I mean, this is
just beautiful.
Wow. This is really soft.
$350?!
Down from $700.
You're saving, like, 200 bucks.
Both logic and math
are taking a serious hit today.
Hey, check this out.
It's totally you.
Wow.
Wow, actually,
this looks pretty good.
Yeah.
"Boys will be boys"?
What? They will be.
All right, that's it.
I'm getting out of here.
No, no, Ross, wait.
Come on, all right?
You know what, there's
other stuff here.
Some nice shirts, look
at these nice pants.
Actually, these might look
pretty good on me.
Yes, they will.
You know what
you should do?
Just go take a walk.
I know your size,
and I'm gonna pick out some
really good stuff for you.
Really?
Yes. And I know what
looks sexy on guys.
Please, just wear
what I suggest
and she is gonna
go nuts for you.
So you're saying
if I wear these pants
I might be getting
into hers?
Why do men keep talking
to me like this?
So, the fact that I'm a doctor
and my wife is a reverend,
that's important to you?
Yeah, I read
some great applications.
But then I thought,
who better than a minister
to raise a child?
Amen.
Plus, I thought the baby would
be in good hands with a doctor.
Good hands.
Healing hands.
Reverend, can I ask?
Does the Bible say anything
about adoption?
It says do it.
"And behold, she did adopt
unto them a baby.
And it was good."
Wow.
Yeah. Wow.
I was wondering,
you both have such serious jobs.
Would you have time to take care
of a baby and your flock?
No, my flock...
my flock is good.
Yeah, my flock pretty much
takes care of themselves
by this point.
Good flock.
Flock, flock, flock.
But being a doctor,
that must take up a lot of time.
Not for me, it doesn't.
So, how's everything
going in here?
We're great.
I think I may have
asked all my questions.
Well, do you have
any questions for Erica?
Yeah, actually.
So, you read a file
that you liked,
and then you gave the
agency the serial number,
and they contacted us?
Yes, our system insures
total anonymity.
We're very proud of it.
You should be.
You're really
on top of stuff.
Well, then if there's
nothing else,
then the two of us
should talk.
I actually...
I don't think
we have to.
You don't?
Yeah, when I read
about you two
I was pretty sure
I wanted you.
But I just thought
we should meet
face to face.
I've made my decision.
I choose them.
Oh, my God, this is great.
This is so great.
Did you hear that?
Yeah. I did.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You are so going to heaven!
We got some really
great stuff.
Yeah. Yeah, but I'm
not sure about some
of the bras I got.
Oh, really? Do you want to try
some of them on for me?
Oh, okay.
Wait, are we in
Joey's imagination?
Oh, no.
I took one of Ross' bags
by mistake.
And one of mine is missing.
Oh, well, Ross probably
has it.
You can get it
from him later.
So... what do you think?
I think we're not wearing
the same shirt anymore.
Yeah. Yeah, Rachel
picked it out for me.
She told me to trust her,
and you know what,
I'm glad I did.
I turned quite a few heads
on my way over here.
Dude, I really don't think
you should be wearing that.
Oh, I see.
Somebody's afraid of little
competition with the ladies?
Looks like someone
is the ladies.
You're just jealous
because you couldn't
pull this off.
Yeah. Now if you'll
excuse me, I have a date.
See, all eyes on me.
We are not
signing those papers.
Why not?
It's wrong.
They made a mistake.
They think we're somebody else.
God works in mysterious ways.
You have got to stop.
But she liked us.
She likes Dr. Chandler
and Reverend Monica.
If you think about it,
I'm kind of like a reverend.
I mean, as a chef,
I serve God by feeding
the hungry and poor.
Your veal chop is $34.95.
Come on, Chandler, I think we've
been given an opportunity.
The mistake has
already been made.
They're writing up the papers
right now.
But we're not the one
she chose.
How can you feel
okay about this?
Because...
We may not be who
she thinks we are,
but no one will ever love
that baby more than us.
I know.
I mean, who knows how long
it's going to take
for someone else to give us
a baby?
What if no one ever picks us?
Oh, honey...
Please.
Please, we are so close.
Monica, I want a baby, too,
but this woman is giving away
her child.
She deserves to know
who it's going to.
Okay, you're right.
So, we'll tell the truth,
and who knows,
you know, maybe she'll
like us for us.
Maybe she will.
Why couldn't I have
been a reverend?
You're Jewish.
Technicality.
Garden salad for the lady.
Oh, that looks great.
Good ordering.
Seafood platter
for the gentleman,
and extra fries.
Enjoy.
Mm, those fries look delicious.
Oh, I didn't know
you liked French fries.
Help yourself.
What's mine is yours.
Oh, wow,
are those stuffed clams?
Uh, yes they are
my stuffed clams.
How about those fries,
though, huh?
They're delicious.
You are beautiful,
you know that?
That is so sweet.
Okay, yeah.
Now look what you did!
What is the matter with you?
I don't like it when people
take food off of my plate, okay?
But you just said
what's mine is yours.
Well, I didn't mean it!
Fine. Sorry.
I didn't think it was
that big a deal.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm overreacting, okay?
It's just... when it comes to
food I have certain rules, okay?
I mean,
there are things you do and, you
know, things that you don't do.
Wow. This place looks great.
Oh, you are going to love it.
And I'm glad we're
finally doing this.
Me, too.
Here.
So this was fun.
Look, I really am sorry
about, you know, before,
and I just want
to make sure you know
that I really do like you.
Sure. Just not as much as clams.
Well, stuffed clams.
Chocolate torte
for the lady.
Cheesecake for the gentleman.
Excuse me, sir.
There seems to be some sort
of red crap on my cheesecake.
Oh, yes, that's
a raspberry coulis.
I'm so stupid
ordering cheesecake.
Trying to be healthy.
Oh, my God. Mm!
All right, I'll just have
what she's having instead.
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
That was our last piece.
Mm, mm.
( beeping )
Oh, no.
This is work.
I should call in.
Can you excuse me?
Oh, yeah, sure, no problem.
What are you doing?
I thought you don't share food.
Sure I do.
Coulis?
No.
If I can't have your clams,
you can't have my dessert.
This is a two-way street.
( chuckles )
Really?
Really.
Now this all better
be here when I come back.
Yeah, of course.
I can control myself.
Stop staring at me!
Oh, just a tiny little...
Uh-oh.
I'm not even sorry.
Hi.
Hey.
So these are
the preliminary forms
for an open adoption.
There's a lot
to go over,
but I'll explain
everything as
we go through.
Is that... is that
a picture?
Yeah, it's a sonogram
they took of the baby last week.
I thought you
might want to see it.
Look, Doctor.
Look, before we
sign anything,
we really have to talk.
We're not who
you think we are.
I don't understand.
The agency must have
made some mistake.
My wife is
not a reverend,
and I'm not a doctor.
What?
That's impossible.
I could perform
an operation on you
and prove it if you'd like.
I have to check your file.
Excuse me.
So, who are you?
Well, our names really are
Monica and Chandler.
We're from New York.
But the important thing
to know about us
is how much we would care
for this little baby.
So, you lied to me before?
Well, we
"bore false witness."
See? I could be
a reverend.
I can't believe this.
We were hoping that since
we told you the truth,
that you still might
consider...
Giving you my baby?
You think I'd give you
my child after this?!
You don't have to decide
right now.
But if you could just
look at our file...
I don't want to look
at your file!
This is over.
Erica, wait.
I have nothing
to say to you.
You have every reason
to be upset.
We did lie,
but only because
we've been waiting
and trying to have baby
for so long.
And we don't know how long
it's going to be
before we get
another chance again.
Why don't you ask the reverend
to pray on it.
Erica, please.
Just consider us.
Ask them to see our file.
Our last name's Bing.
My wife's a chef
and I'm in advertising.
Oh, yeah.
I actually liked you guys.
It doesn't matter,
because what you did was wrong.
But you did like us.
And you should.
My wife's an incredible woman.
She's loving and devoted
and caring.
And don't tell her I said this,
but the woman's always right.
I love my wife more than
anything in this world.
And it... it kills me that
I can't give her a baby.
I really want a kid.
And when that day
finally comes,
I'll learn how to be a good dad.
But my wife...
she's already there.
She's a mother...
without a baby.
Please.
You still want
that baby?
God bless you,
Chandler Bing!
Turns out this sweater is
made for a woman.
So, why are you
still wearing it?
Because it's soft.
Hey, so how was your date?
Not so good.
Well, looks like
it's just the two of us
tonight, huh, buddy?
Yeah, and you know what?
We could do a lot worse.
Yeah.
Joey doesn't share food!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org